[{"answer": "You shouldn't be! Yeah, Hallowee", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Me too, I'm jus", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Me too, I'm jus", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "It is sooo refreshing to hear you say that, because isn't that what everyone thinks but is afraid to say? I mean, i's science. I'", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Uh, wow. Yes! Of course! Yes! My God. I've never been in a wedding", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I know what you're doing. Don't downplay this. I'm happy for you. And someday when hell freezes over and I get married, you can be my Maid of Honor. But for right now, this is about you. OK? This is you're day, and it is a big deal", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Bridal Party", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What!? I've never even heard of that", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You just admitted it", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You admitted it.  Yeah, I can't do that though", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Yes? Who is this", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend?! Hiiii", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know about you but since we're at a that place restaurant, I'm gonna try the dog. my friend laughs at his own joke and continues drinking", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I try to squeeze in a game now and then. We should play sometime", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Leader of the bridesmaids? Um, wouldn't that technically be me? Honor", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Oh, well, what about a nice pen..or a tortois", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, I don't know. Everybody always goes to that place. It seems just cliche to me", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Where's my friend", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Oh. She's meeting us there", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hello!", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yeah, I'm fine. I'm here! Where are you?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Shut the fuck up or I will kick your ass bitch", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "And what are you forty", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, ", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I wasn't sick. my friend told you that because... I couldn't afford to go with you guys", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "That's funny. You know what? As the Maid of honor, which is what I am and what you are not, I am asking you to just give us a minute", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No, excuse me", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "No, excuse me", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I need to take it easy", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I'm telling you I am not jealous of my friend, okay? She's tall and thin and rich and pretty. They both laugh", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh yeah, I got it goin' on..", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "It's okay. I really am sorry", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Well its easy to get caught up", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "So, did you get the moonpies", "docId": "Bridesmaids.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Did you like' em", "qsentId": 36}]